PERSONAL INFO

Phone 07780341618

Email swanzyflexy@gmail.com

WEBSITES & SOCIAL LINKS

LinkedIn

SKILLS

Technical Support

Building/Configuring System

Network Installations

IT Service Desk

End User Support

Customer Communication

Positive attitude and willingness to learn quickly

User Training

PROFESSIONAL COURSES

Introduction to DevOps

cousera Jan 2023 - Feb 2023

Introduction to Cloud Computing

cousera Mar 2023 - Apr 2023

Introduction to Agile Development and Scrum

cousera May 2023 - Jun 2023

Introduction to Software Engineering

cousera Jun 2023 - Jul 2023

HOBBIES

Sports music

Mutiu Adeniyi

IT Support Engineer

Goal-Oriented IT support Engineer with track record of delivering technical support and customer care to clients, maintaining various Pc hard and Software and Coordinating new personnel. Experience in Object Oriented programing, code development, testing and debugging, interface design, system and network administrator. Proactive dynamic and a skilled troubleshooter, with a strong emphasis on developing and implementing process improvement to support company growth and technical innovation.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

IT Support Engineer | Jul 2021 - Aug 2023 Nobtec Ltd, UK

- Assist with testing and provide feedback on the overall end-user experience.
- Measure, report and drive IT support KPIs.
- Guide, Mentor and support IT support teammates.
- Responsible for resolving support requests and service tickets.
- Respond to technical support calls from other staff members or clients and communicate how to resolve issues.
- Keep a record of issues, along with solutions, to refer back to in future instances.
- Support the roll-out of new applications.
- Install and configure computer hardware, software, networks and applications.

IT Administrator | Apr 2020 - May 2021 Kaslee Royal Integrated Service

- Monitor and maintain computer systems and networks.
- Relate with staff and clients through a to help set up systems or resolve issues.
- Troubleshoot system and network problems.
- Installing and configuring software, hardware and networks.
- Ensuring security and efficiency of IT infrastructure.

web developer | May 2017 - Jan 2021 wipro

- Writing efficient code using best practice for software development.
- Creating websites using different languages such as HTML and CSS.
- Working with Programmers and Web Designers to create a website that matches the visual design intent.
- Communicating with business colleagues to gather and refine requirements and specifications for content development within agreed-upon timelines.
- Researching a variety of software programs.
- Improving and enhancing websites after they have been created.

Full Stack Developer | Aug 2019 - May 2020 Kaslee Royal Integrated Service

LANGUAGES

English

- Developing front end website architecture.
- Designing user interactions on web pages.
- Developing back-end website applications.
- Creating servers and databases for functionality.
- Ensuring cross-platform optimization for mobile phones.
- Ensuring responsiveness of applications.

EDUCATION

Bachelor | Jun 2014 - May 2017 Bengaluru University, Bangalore

Bachelor of Computer Application CGPA: 6.1(first class)

INTERNSHIPS

Android AppDevelopment | Aug 2016 - Aug 2017 Internet Academy

- Design and build advanced applications for the Android platform.
- Collaborate with cross-functional teams to define, design, and ship new features.
- Work with outside data sources and APIs.
- Unit-test code for robustness, including edge cases, usability, and general reliability.

AWS developer and Cyberneticist

cyberneticist

- Developing algorithms and software to manage and regulate system behaviors
- Developing new theories, models, and frameworks to explain and predict system dynamics.
- Designing and implementing control systems for various applications, such as robotics, manufacturing, aerospace, and more.

AWS Developer

- Plan and monitor the AWS cloud infrastructure.
- Build and configure the production systems.
- Manage updating process of the server-based technologies
- Coordinate with architecture teams to design new software technologies for clients.
- Test and implement constant updates while identifying improvement opportunities.